

Hambura, Germany

🛘 +49-177-6028021 | 💆 connect@chetanbhasin.com | 🛠 chetanbhasin.com | 🖸 Chetanbhasin | 🛅 chetanbhasin | 💆 @Chetanbhasin

"Software should be reproducible and prevent human errors."

# Summary.

I am currently self-employed and working for a long term client on primarily offering backend development in Rust. Apart from that, I like Nix & Functional Programming, and have extensive experience working with Kubernetes and solving other DevOps problems for growing companies.

## Skills

Operations NixOS, Kubernetes, Terraform, AWS, Packer, Vault, Grafana Toolkit (Tempo, Dashboard, etc.)

Front-end NextJS, TailWind, TypeScript, React **Programming** Rust, Scala, Golang, Haskell, Python

# Work Experience \_\_

**Confidential Client** Remote/Hamburg, Germany

SOFTWARE CONSULTANT Sep. 2022 - Present

· Provided comprehensive Rust development, testing, and reviewing services. Unfortunately, the rest is confidential.

Jimdo GmbH Hambura

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Sep. 2020 - Sep. 2022

- Built a Kubernetes operator to deploy and monitor services with low developer effort.
- Helped advance CI & CD tooling on top of GitHub.
- Supported with several infrastructure & software related topis such as secrets management, vault, Terraformm, Kubernetes, & cloud networking.

**Enfore AG** Hamburg, Germany

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Nov. 2018 - Sep. 2020

- · Implementing tooling for code derivation from specification focusing on developer productivity and safety.
- Designed and built the authentication and authorisation framework for enterprise APIs team.
- Helped migrate and advocate a streamlined deployment process on top of Kubernetes

Akanoo GmbH Hamburg, Germany

Feb. 2018 - Nov. 2018 SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- · Helped build and maintain features on a distributed tracking backend built on message passing and state machine design.
- · Managed and helped maintain live updating data pipelines digested by our distributed tracking system.

Relink A/s Copenhagen, Denmark

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Sep. 2016 - Jan. 2018

- Built from scratch an in house service ecosystem platform on top of Kubernetes focused on ease of use and developer productivity.
- Implemented backend service and data collection pipelines to support data sciende and machine learning teams.
- · Migrated several services running on Apache Mesos and provisioned to Kubernetes along with Drone Cl.

### Atlan (formerly SocialCops)

New Delhi, India Sep. 2015 - Sep. 2016

SOFTWARE ENGINEE (BACKEND & INFRASTRUCTURE)

- · Built and maintain a hurestics based human language search and autocomplete engine on top of structured data.
- Helped streamline developer workflows by improving tooling and automating common tasks on CI.
- Built several data flow pipelines and automation jobs for structured and unstructured data.
- · Built an experimental data cataloging engine.

# Education

MSI (IP University) New Delhi, India

BACH. COMPUTER APPLICATIONS 2012 - 2015

- · Participated in Computer Society of India.
- Organised tech festivals and coding competitions.

CHETAN BHASIN · RÉSUMÉ APRIL 23, 2023